<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Shaheer Muzammil</title>
    <link>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Shaheer Muzammil</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 18:56:13 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Organically DevOps: Building Quality and Security into the Software Supply Chain at Liberty Mutual</title>
      <link>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/publications/alldaydevops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/publications/alldaydevops/</guid>
      <description>This talk looked at Liberty Mutual’s transformation to Continuous Integration, Continuous Delivery, and DevOps. For a large, heavily regulated industry, this task can not only be daunting, but viewed by many as impossible. Often, organizations try to reduce the friction through micro-fixes, but Eddie’s team asked how to change the culture to reduce the friction and concluded with the following final points:
 Don’t mandate DevOps. Give employees the chance to master their discipline with examples to set and follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhotoTune by VYRO AI</title>
      <link>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/projects/phototune/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/projects/phototune/</guid>
      <description>PhotoTune is a photo enhancement tool by Vyro AI that gathered more than Half a million downloads in less than a quarter of its release in early 2022.
PhotoTunes&amp;rsquo;s main features:
 Super resolute your photoes to 2x/3x/4x resolution Beautify your portraits by removing blemishes, smoothing your skin and adding HDR HDR delivers a higher contrast photo with reduced haze and noise Colorise adds color to old and black &amp;amp; white photos  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhotoStudio by VYRO AI</title>
      <link>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/projects/photostudio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/projects/photostudio/</guid>
      <description>Photo Studio is an all-in-one pro photo editing application with creative tool to stylise and enhance your images with 1M+ downloads since its inception in June 2021.
PhotoStudio Main Features:
 Crop the Photos to any dimension and adjust it for any social platform you want to share Use trending filters for your photos and popular filter categories available Use Sky Changer feature and replace sky from your photos to beautiful skies Use the Background eraser feature to erase and replace 100+ backgrounds Use Cloths feature to change Texture of your cloths to new stylish textures Use Adjustment tool to adjust and polish your photos Use LightFx to beautify photos with transparent Overlays Add text to photos with 100+ unique fonts Add stickers to pictures and create your own stickers Use Defocus Blur backgrounds feature to provide depth blur effects Enhance Photos up to 2x and 4x.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ReTeam by BeRemote LLC</title>
      <link>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/projects/reteam-by-beremote-llc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/projects/reteam-by-beremote-llc/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SURF TV</title>
      <link>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/projects/surf-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/projects/surf-tv/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SURF Rideshare</title>
      <link>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/projects/surf-rideshare/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/projects/surf-rideshare/</guid>
      <description>An entertainment platform that places interactive tablets in ride-share vehicles for the entertainment of passengers and the promotion of local businesses and brands which provides;
 Free Video content to stream by Media gaints like Paramount Pictures, Vevo and many famous content creators like Tasty, The Daily Show, etc. Full iHeart Radio experience where the riders can listen to iHearts best Radio station, their favourite artists and highly engaging podcasts. Free coupons and disounts to nearby stores and shops  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recording</title>
      <link>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/projects/recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 12:41:05 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/projects/recording/</guid>
      <description>A simple android voice recording application I created a while back. It has following features;
 Record audio. Pause/Resume between a recording. Control recording bitrate. Save recording to local storage in a folder named Recording. View, Rename or delete all recordings.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GeoTrack</title>
      <link>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/projects/geo-track/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2017 12:41:05 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/projects/geo-track/</guid>
      <description>GeoTrack GeoTrack is an Attendance monitoring and location tracking application using Google Geofences it will record user&amp;rsquo;s enterance and exit from user specific server defined Geofences. It also has a location tracking service that collects user&amp;rsquo;s location with an interval of 15 minutes and is triggered and stopped on the bases of three criterias, that are;
 Continuous: never stops Fence based trigger: starts and ends service when the person enters a particular fence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vesta Audit</title>
      <link>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/projects/vesta-audit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 12:41:05 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/projects/vesta-audit/</guid>
      <description>The application replaces manual telecom tower surveys. By digitalizing survey form data entry, syncing and report generation for multiple survey roles like Power Engineer, Civil, Design, etc.
This application was sold to MTN Nigeria and JAZZ (The largest telecom services provider in Pakistan).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer Insight</title>
      <link>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/projects/customer-insight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 12:41:05 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shaheermuzammil.com/projects/customer-insight/</guid>
      <description>Customer Insight Customer insight was a multi language application for Telecom Industry to monitor their network user&amp;rsquo;s experience and improve customer support. The application was meant to collect user&amp;rsquo;s network performance parameters to build coverage maps and find weak areas. The application also enabled the user to run call sms and internet speed tests for runtime diagnostics.
Application Screens The application UI was based on a View Pager an the user could swipe through the dashboard and test screens.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>